hey guys I love this problem it says the
width is twice the height if the
perimeter is 120 what is the area and
we're given that the width is x^2 - x -
16 and the height is x + 12 if you want
to try this on your own pause it right
now cuz I'm going to solve it in 3 2 1
these are a trap we don't need these so
we can just assign H for the height and
call the width 2 H because the width is
twice the height so we need the
perimeter to be 120 that means we need H
+ 2 H + H + 2 H to equal 120 and H H + 2
H + H + 2 H is equal to 6 h after we
divide both sides by 6 we get H equal to
20 so we can plug in 20 for these H's
and the two h's will become 40 40 + 20 +
40 + 20 gives us 120 and then the area
will be 40 * 20 which is 800 unit
squared and that's the answer to the
question how exciting